Henry-Russell Hitchcock
Archives of American Art, Smithsonian Institution
- Chronological Name and Subject Files, 1919-1987, Series 2:; (Boxes 1-22; 21.9 linear ft.)
  Wittmann, Otto (1952, 1964)
  Witwatersrand, University of the (1948-1950)
  WNET, Channel Thirteen (see: Thirteen, WNET)
  Woburn Public Library (1936)
  Wofsy, Alan (1982)
  Wolf, Gertrude (1952)
  Wolf, J. Robert (1962)
  Wolf, Peter M. (1965, 1970)
  Wolf, Reva (1980)
  Wolfe, Christopher (1977)
  Wolfe, R. (1963)
  Wolff, Michael (1957)
  Wollman, Henry (1971, 1973, 1976-1978)
  Wood, Barbara L. (1950)
  Wood, Charles B. (1971, 1974)
  Wood, W. L. (1941)
  Wood, Welby Carter (1970)
  Woodbridge, Henry (1949)
  Woodhouse, Lawrence M. (1965, 1984)
  Woodring, Carl (1971)
  Woodrow Wilson Foundation (1969-1970)
  Woodside, Joan (1974-1980, 1983-1984, 1986)
  Woolf, Virginia (1927)
  Worbs, Dietrich (1982-1983)
  Worcester Art Museum (1947, 1981)
  World Construction Program (1957)
  World Crossroads of Learning, Inc. (1965)
  World Publishing Co. (1952, 1967)
  World Writing (1953)
  Wortman, Julie (1974)
  Wrenn, George (1959)
  Wright, Benjamin F. (1949, 1951)
  Wright, David (1950-1952)
  Wright, Frank Lloyd (1937, 1942-1943, 1945, 1947, 1950-1953, 1957-1958, 1978, 1980, 1982-1983, undated)
  Wright, Mrs. Frank Lloyd (1959)
  Wright, Frank Lloyd, Home and Studio Foundation (1977, 1984)
  Wright, Frank Lloyd, and In the Nature of Materials (1941)
  Wright, John Lloyd (1968)
  Wriston, Barbara (1952-1953, 1956, 1960, 1962, 1967)
  Wurm, Heinrich (1966)
  Wurster, William W. (1943-1944, 1946,-1948, 1950, 1951-1957, 1959, 1961)
  Wurster, William W. and Catherine 1945
  Wyoming, University of (1975)
  Xenakis, Jason (1958)
  Yale Review (1966-1968, 1970)
  Yale University (1947-1960, 1962-1963, 1965-1979, 1982, 1986)
  Yardley, Michael (1975-1978)
  Yeon, John (1954)
  York City Art Gallery (1958)
  York Institute of Architectural Study (1957-1959, 1961)
  York, University of (1962, 1970)
  Yorke, R.F.S. (1952)
  Youell, William (1948)
  Young, E. A. (1947)
  Young, Elaine (1962)
  Young, Elizabeth (1961)
  Young, Paul E. (1949)
  Young, Mr. and Mrs. Wilfred B. (1954-1955)
  Youritzin, Glenda Green (1974)
  Zacchwatowicz, Jim (1963)
  Zador, Anna (1970, 1972)
  Zarnecki, George (1953)
  Zaroff, Anne T. (1975)
  Zawisa, Bernard J. (1952-1953, 1956)
  Zenith Corp. (1969-1970)
  Zenobi Sarto (1963)
  Zerkowitz, A. (1957)
  Zevi, Bruno (1952)
  Zewicher, Mrs. Victor K. (1950)
  Zimmerman Brothers (1963-1966, 1969)
  Zimmerman, Mrs. Isadore (1952)
  Zodiac Revue (1959-1969)
  Zorn, Kate (1979)
  Zubarec, Michael (1956-1957)
  Zwemmer, A. (1946-1948, 1955, 1959)
  - Correspondence, 1919 (Box 1)
  - Correspondence, 1920 (Box 1)
  - Correspondence, 1922 (Box 1)
  - Correspondence,1923 (Box 1)
  - Correspondence, 1924 (Box 1)
  - Correspondence, 1925 (Box 1)
  - Correspondence, 1926 (Box 1)
  - Correspondence, A-J, 1927 (Box 1)
  - Correspondence, K, 1927 (Box 1)
  - Correspondence, M-P, 1927 (Box 1)
  - Correspondence, Smith, Peter van der Meulen, circa 1927-1928, (2 folders) (Box 1)
  - Correspondence, Sn-W, 1927 (Box 1)
  - Correspondence, Unknown and Illegible, 1927 (Box 1)
  - Correspondence, A-B, 1928 (Box 1)
  - Correspondence, C-H, 1928 (Box 1)
  - Correspondence, Kates, George, 1928, (2 folders) (Box 1)
  - Correspondence, Ki-M, 1928 (Box 1)
  - Correspondence, N-Sm, 1928 (Box 1)
  - Correspondence, Smith, Peter, 1928, (4 folders) (Box 1)
  - Correspondence, St-Z, 1928 (Box 1)
  - Correspondence, Illegible and Unknown, 1928 (Box 1)
  - Correspondence, F-H, 1929 (Box 1)
  - Correspondence, K-P, 1929 (Box 1)
  - Correspondence, S-Z, 1929 (Box 1)
  - Correspondence, 1930 (Box 1)
  - Correspondence, 1931 (Box 1)
  - Correspondence, 1932 (Box 1)
  - 19th Century American Architecture - Research Inquiries (with Philip Johnson), 1932 (Box 1)
  - Correspondence, 1933 (Box 1)
  - Correspondence, 1934 (Box 1)
  - Correspondence, 1935 (Box 1)
  - Correspondence, 1936 (Box 1)
  - Correspondence, 1937 (Box 1)
  - Correspondence, A-Z, 1938 (Box 2)
  - Correspondence, A-Z, 1939 (Box 2)
  - Correspondence, Rhode Island Exhibition, 1939 (Box 2)
  - Correspondence, A-Z, 1940 (Box 2)
  - Correspondence, A-M, 1941 (Box 2)
  - Correspondence, N-Z, 1941 (Box 2)
  - Correspondence, About F.L Wright and In the Nature of Materials, 1941 (Box 2)
  - Correspondence, A-H, 1942 (Box 2)
  - Correspondence, L-Z, 1942 (Box 2)
  - Correspondence, War Service Appointment, 1942 (Box 2)
  - Correspondence, A-Z, 1943 (Box 2)
  - Correspondence, War Service Appointment, 1943 (Box 2)
  - Correspondence, A-Z, 1944 (Box 2)
  - Correspondence, A-Al, 1945 (Box 2)
  - Correspondence, Am-As, 1945 (Box 2)
  - Correspondence, B, 1945 (Box 2)
  - Correspondence, C, 1945 (Box 2)
  - Correspondence, D-E, 1945 (Box 2)
  - Correspondence, F, 1945 (Box 2)
  - Correspondence, G, 1945 (Box 2)
  - Correspondence, H, 1945 (Box 2)
  - Correspondence, I-L, 1945 (Box 2)
  - Correspondence, M, 1945 (Box 2)
  - Correspondence, N-Q, 1945 (Box 2)
  - Correspondence, R, 1945 (Box 2)
  - Correspondence, S, 1945 (Box 2)
  - Correspondence, T-V, 1945 (Box 2)
  - Correspondence, W, 1945 (Box 2)
  - Correspondence, Illegible and Unknown, 1945 (Box 2)
  - Correspondence, A, 1946 (Box 2)
  - Correspondence, B, 1946 (Box 2)
  - Correspondence, C, 1946 (Box 2)
  - Correspondence, D-E, 1946 (Box 2)
  - Correspondence, F-G, 1946 (Box 2)
  - Correspondence, H, 1946 (Box 2)
  - Correspondence, J-K, 1946 (Box 2)
  - Correspondence, L, 1946 (Box 2)
  - Correspondence, M, 1946 (Box 2)
  - Correspondence, N-O, 1946 (Box 2)
  - Correspondence, P, 1946 (Box 3)
  - Correspondence, R, 1946 (Box 3)
  - Correspondence, S, 1946 (Box 3)
  - Correspondence, T, 1946 (Box 3)
  - Correspondence, U-V, 1946 (Box 3)
  - Correspondence, W-Z, 1946 (Box 3)
  - Correspondence, Illegible and Unknown, 1946 (Box 3)
  - Correspondence, A, 1947 (Box 3)
  - Correspondence, B, 1947 (Box 3)
  - Correspondence, Ca-Con, 1947 (Box 3)
  - Correspondence, Coo-Cu, 1947 (Box 3)
  - Correspondence, D-E, 1947 (Box 3)
  - Correspondence, F, 1947 (Box 3)
  - Correspondence, G, 1947 (Box 3)
  - Correspondence, H, 1947 (Box 3)
  - Correspondence, I-K, 1947 (Box 3)
  - Correspondence, L, 1947 (Box 3)
  - Correspondence, M, 1947 (Box 3)
  - Correspondence, N-O, 1947 (Box 3)
  - Correspondence, P-Q, 1947 (Box 3)
  - Correspondence, R, 1947 (Box 3)
  - Correspondence, S, 1947 (Box 3)
  - Correspondence, T-V, 1947 (Box 3)
  - Correspondence, W-Z, 1947 (Box 3)
  - Correspondence, Illegible and Unknown, 1947 (Box 3)
  - Correspondence, A, 1948 (Box 3)
  - Correspondence, B, 1948 (Box 3)
  - Correspondence, Ca-Cl, 1948 (Box 3)
  - Correspondence, Co-Cu, 1948 (Box 3)
  - Correspondence, D-E, 1948 (Box 3)
  - Correspondence, F, 1948 (Box 3)
  - Correspondence, H, 1948 (Box 3)
  - Correspondence, I-L, 1948 (Box 3)
  - Correspondence, Ma-Mi, 1948 (Box 3)
  - Correspondence, Miller Co-Mum, 1948 (Box 3)
  - Correspondence, Museum of Modern Art, 1948 (Box 3)
  - Correspondence, N-O, 1948 (Box 3)
  - Correspondence, P, 1948 (Box 3)
  - Correspondence, R, 1948 (Box 3)
  - Correspondence, So-Su, 1948 (Box 3)
  - Correspondence, T-V, 1948 (Box 3)
  - Correspondence, W-Z; Illegible and Unknown, 1948 (Box 3)
  - Correspondence, A, 1949 (Box 4)
  - Correspondence, B, 1949 (Box 4)
  - Correspondence, C, 1949 (Box 4)
  - Correspondence, D, 1949 (Box 4)
  - Correspondence, F-G, 1949 (Box 4)
  - Correspondence, H, 1949 (Box 4)
  - Correspondence, I-K, 1949 (Box 4)
  - Correspondence, M-Mil, 1949 (Box 4)
  - Correspondence, Min-Mus, 1949 (Box 4)
  - Correspondence, N-O, 1949 (Box 4)
  - Correspondence, P, 1949 (Box 4)
  - Correspondence, L, 1949 (Box 4)
  - Correspondence, R, 1949 (Box 4)
  - Correspondence, S, 1949 (Box 4)
  - Correspondence, T-V, 1949 (Box 4)
  - Correspondence, W-Z, 1949 (Box 4)
  - Correspondence, Illegible and Unknown, 1949 (Box 4)
  - Correspondence, A, 1950 (Box 4)
  - Correspondence, B, 1950 (Box 4)
  - Correspondence, C, 1950 (Box 4)
  - Correspondence, D-E, 1950 (Box 4)
  - Correspondence, F, 1950 (Box 4)
  - Correspondence, G, 1950 (Box 4)
  - Correspondence, H, 1950 (Box 4)
  - Correspondence, I-K, 1950 (Box 4)
  - Correspondence, L, 1950 (Box 4)
  - Correspondence, M, 1950 (Box 4)
  - Correspondence, N-O, 1950 (Box 4)
  - Correspondence, P, 1950 (Box 4)
  - Correspondence, R, 1950 (Box 4)
  - Correspondence, S-So, 1950 (Box 4)
  - Correspondence, St, 1950 (Box 4)
  - Correspondence, T-V, 1950 (Box 4)
  - Correspondence, W, 1950 (Box 4)
  - Correspondence, A, 1951 (Box 4)
  - Correspondence, B, 1951 (Box 4)
  - Correspondence, California, University of, 1951 (Box 4)
  - Correspondence, Ch-Cu, 1951 (Box 4)
  - Correspondence, D-E, 1951 (Box 4)
  - Correspondence, F-G, 1951 (Box 4)
  - Correspondence, H-J, 1951 (Box 4)
  - Correspondence, K, 1951 (Box 5)
  - Correspondence, L, 1951 (Box 5)
  - Correspondence, M, 1951 (Box 5)
  - Correspondence, N-O, 1951 (Box 5)
  - Correspondence, Paxton Drawings, 1951-1952 (Box 5)
  - Correspondence, P, 1951 (Box 5)
  - Correspondence, R, 1951 (Box 5)
  - Correspondence, S, 1951 (Box 5)
  - Correspondence, T-V, 1951 (Box 5)
  - Correspondence, W-Z, 1951 (Box 5)
  - Correspondence, Illegible and Unknown, 1951 (Box 5)
  - Correspondence, A, 1952 (Box 5)
  - Correspondence, B, 1952 (Box 5)
  - Correspondence, C, 1952 (Box 5)
  - Correspondence, Christmas Cards, 1952 (Box 5)
  - Correspondence, Condolence on Death of Mother, 1952 (Box 5)
  - Correspondence, D, 1952 (Box 5)
  - Correspondence, E-F, 1952 (Box 5)
  - Correspondence, G, 1952 (Box 5)
  - Correspondence, H, 1952 (Box 5)
  - Correspondence, I-J, 1952 (Box 5)
  - Correspondence, K, 1952 (Box 5)
  - Correspondence, L, 1952 (Box 5)
  - Correspondence, Ma, 1952 (Box 5)
  - Correspondence, Me-Mu, 1952 (Box 5)
  - Correspondence, N-O, 1952 (Box 5)
  - Correspondence, P, 1952 (Box 5)
  - Correspondence, R, 1952 (Box 5)
  - Correspondence, S, 1952 (Box 5)
  - Correspondence, T-V, 1952 (Box 5)
  - Correspondence, W, 1952 (Box 5)
  - Correspondence, Y-Z, 1952 (Box 5)
  - Correspondence, Unknown and Illegible, 1952 (Box 5)
  - Correspondence, A, 1953 (Box 5)
  - Correspondence, B, 1953 (Box 5)
  - Correspondence, C, 1953 (Box 5)
  - Correspondence, D-E, 1953 (Box 5)
  - Correspondence, F, 1953 (Box 5)
  - Correspondence, G, 1953 (Box 5)
  - Correspondence, H, 1953 (Box 6)
  - Correspondence, I-J, 1953 (Box 6)
  - Correspondence, K, 1953 (Box 6)
  - Correspondence, L, 1953 (Box 6)
  - Correspondence, M, 1953 (Box 6)
  - Correspondence, N-O, 1953 (Box 6)
  - Correspondence, P-Q, 1953 (Box 6)
  - Correspondence, R, 1953 (Box 6)
  - Correspondence, S, 1953 (Box 6)
  - Correspondence, T-V, 1953 (Box 6)
  - Correspondence, W, 1953 (Box 6)
  - Correspondence, X-Z, 1953 (Box 6)
  - Correspondence, Illegible and Unknown, 1953 (Box 6)
  - Correspondence, A, 1954 (Box 6)
  - Correspondence, B, 1954 (Box 6)
  - Correspondence, C, 1954 (Box 6)
  - Correspondence, D-E, 1954 (Box 6)
  - Correspondence, F, 1954 (Box 6)
  - Correspondence, G, 1954 (Box 6)
  - Correspondence, H, 1954 (Box 6)
  - Correspondence, I-K, 1954 (Box 6)
  - Correspondence, L, 1954 (Box 6)
  - Correspondence, M, 1954 (Box 6)
  - Correspondence, N-O, 1954 (Box 6)
  - Correspondence, P, 1954 (Box 6)
  - Correspondence, R, 1954 (Box 6)
  - Correspondence, S, 1954 (Box 6)
  - Correspondence, T-V, 1954 (Box 6)
  - Correspondence, W, 1954 (Box 6)
  - Correspondence, Y-Z, 1954 (Box 6)
  - Correspondence, Illegible and Unknown, 1954 (Box 6)
  - Correspondence, A, 1955 (Box 6)
  - Correspondence, B, 1955 (Box 6)
  - Correspondence, C, 1955 (Box 6)
  - Correspondence, D, 1955 (Box 6)
  - Correspondence, E-F, 1955 (Box 6)
  - Correspondence, G, 1955 (Box 6)
  - Correspondence, H, 1955 (Box 6)
  - Correspondence, I-J, 1955 (Box 7)
  - Correspondence, K, 1955 (Box 7)
  - Correspondence, L, 1955 (Box 7)
  - Correspondence, M, 1955 (Box 7)
  - Correspondence, Museum of Modern Art, 1955 (Box 7)
  - Correspondence, N-O, 1955 (Box 7)
  - Correspondence, P-Q, 1955 (Box 7)
  - Correspondence, R, 1955 (Box 7)
  - Correspondence, S, 1955 (Box 7)
  - Correspondence, T-V, 1955 (Box 7)
  - Correspondence, W-Z, 1955 (Box 7)
  - Correspondence, Illegible and Unknown, 1955 (Box 7)
  - Correspondence, A, 1956 (Box 7)
  - Correspondence, B, 1956 (Box 7)
  - Correspondence, C, 1956 (Box 7)
  - Correspondence, D, 1956 (Box 7)
  - Correspondence, E-F, 1956 (Box 7)
  - Correspondence, G, 1956 (Box 7)
  - Correspondence, H, 1956 (Box 7)
  - Correspondence, I, 1956 (Box 7)
  - Correspondence, Income Tax, 1956 (Box 7)
  - Correspondence, J, 1956 (Box 7)
  - Correspondence, K-L, 1956 (Box 7)
  - Correspondence, Mac/Mc, 1956 (Box 7)
  - Correspondence, Man-Mun, 1956 (Box 7)
  - Correspondence, Mus-My, 1956 (Box 7)
  - Correspondence, N-O, 1956 (Box 7)
  - Correspondence, Pa-Pe, 1956 (Box 7)
  - Correspondence, Pi-Pr, 1956 (Box 7)
  - Correspondence, Q-R, 1956 (Box 7)
  - Correspondence, Sa-Sm, 1956 (Box 7)
  - Correspondence, Society of Architectural Historians (SAH), 1956 (Box 7)
  - Correspondence, SAH Awards, 1956 (Box 7)
  - Correspondence, SAH-CAA Joint Sessions, 1956 (Box 7)
  - Correspondence, Son-Su, 1956 (Box 7)
  - Correspondence, T, 1956 (Box 8)
  - Correspondence, V, 1956 (Box 8)
  - Correspondence, Wa-Wee, 1956 (Box 8)
  - Correspondence, Welch and Forbes, 1956 (Box 8)
  - Correspondence, Wi-Z, 1956 (Box 8)
  - Correspondence, Illegible and Unknown, 1956 (Box 8)
  - Correspondence, A, 1957 (Box 8)
  - Correspondence, B, 1957 (Box 8)
  - Correspondence, C, 1957 (Box 8)
  - Correspondence, D-E, 1957 (Box 8)
  - Correspondence, F, 1957 (Box 8)
  - Correspondence, Gaudi Exhibition, 1957 (Box 8)
  - Correspondence, G, 1957 (Box 8)
  - Correspondence, H, 1957 (Box 8)
  - Correspondence, Income Tax, 1957 (Box 8)
  - Correspondence, I-J, 1957 (Box 8)
  - Correspondence, K-L, 1957 (Box 8)
  - Correspondence, Maa-Mac/Mc, 1957 (Box 8)
  - Correspondence, Mag-Mu, 1957 (Box 8)
  - Correspondence, N-O, 1957 (Box 8)
  - Correspondence, Pa-Peng, 1957 (Box 8)
  - Correspondence, Penguin Books, 1957-1958 (Box 8)
  - Correspondence, Penn-Pr, 1957 (Box 8)
  - Correspondence, Q-R, 1957 (Box 8)
  - Correspondence, Sa-Soc, 1957 (Box 8)
  - Correspondence, St-Sw, 1957 (Box 8)
  - Correspondence, Toronto, 1957 (Box 8)
  - Correspondence, T-V, 1957 (Box 8)
  - Correspondence, Victorian Studies, 1957 (Box 8)
  - Correspondence, Virginia, 1957 (Box 8)
  - Correspondence, W-Z, 1957 (Box 8)
  - Correspondence, Illegible and Unknown, 1957 (Box 8)
  - Correspondence, A, 1958 (Box 8)
  - Correspondence, B, 1958 (Box 8)
  - Correspondence, C, 1958 (Box 8)
  - Correspondence, D-E, 1958 (Box 8)
  - Correspondence, F-G, 1958 (Box 8)
  - Correspondence, H, 1958 (Box 8)
  - Correspondence, I-K, 1958 (Box 8)
  - Correspondence, L, 1958 (Box 8)
  - Correspondence, Mac/Mc, 1958 (Box 8)
  - Correspondence, Man-Mu, 1958 (Box 8)
  - Correspondence, N-O, 1958 (Box 8)
  - Correspondence, P-Q, 1958 (Box 8)
  - Correspondence, R, 1958 (Box 8)
  - Correspondence, Society of Architectural Historians, 1958 (Box 9)
  - Correspondence, Society of Architectural Historians of Great Britain, 1958 (Box 9)
  - Correspondence, T-V, 1958 (Box 9)
  - Correspondence, W-Z, 1958 (Box 9)
  - Correspondence, Illegible and Unknown, 1958 (Box 9)
  - Correspondence, A, 1959 (Box 9)
  - Correspondence, B, 1959 (Box 9)
  - Correspondence, C, 1959 (Box 9)
  - Correspondence, D-E, 1959 (Box 9)
  - Correspondence, F-G, 1959 (Box 9)
  - Correspondence, H, 1959 (Box 9)
  - Correspondence, Houston, 1959 (Box 9)
  - Correspondence, I-L, 1959 (Box 9)
  - Correspondence, Mac/Mc, 1959 (Box 9)
  - Correspondence, Man-Mu, 1959 (Box 9)
  - Correspondence, New Haven Festival of Arts, 1959 (Box 9)
  - Correspondence, N-O, 1959 (Box 9)
  - Correspondence, P-Q, 1959 (Box 9)
  - Correspondence, R, 1959 (Box 9)
  - Correspondence, Sa-Sm, 1959 (Box 9)
  - Correspondence, So, 1959 (Box 9)
  - Correspondence, T-V, 1959 (Box 9)
  - Correspondence, W, 1959 (Box 9)
  - Correspondence, X-Z, 1959 (Box 9)
  - Correspondence, A, 1960 (Box 9)
  - Correspondence, B, 1960 (Box 9)
  - Correspondence, Ca-Col, 1960 (Box 9)
  - Correspondence, Con-Cun, 1960 (Box 9)
  - Correspondence, D-G, 1960 (Box 9)
  - Correspondence, H, 1960 (Box 9)
  - Correspondence, I, 1960 (Box 9)
  - Correspondence, J, 1960 (Box 9)
  - Correspondence, K-L, 1960 (Box 9)
  - Correspondence, M, 1960 (Box 9)
  - Correspondence, N-O, 1960 (Box 9)
  - Correspondence, P, 1960 (Box 9)
  - Correspondence, R, 1960 (Box 9)
  - Correspondence, Sa-Sob, 1960 (Box 9)
  - Correspondence, Soc-Sw, 1960 (Box 9)
  - Correspondence, Voice of America, 1960 (Box 10)
  - Correspondence, Vos-W, 1960 (Box 10)
  - Correspondence, X-Z, 1960 (Box 10)
  - Correspondence, Ab-Al, 1961 (Box 10)
  - Correspondence, Am-Architecture of American, 1961 (Box 10)
  - Correspondence, "Architecture of H. H. Richardson and His Times" (reprint), 1961 (Box 10)
  - Correspondence, Art-Au, 1961 (Box 10)
  - Correspondence, B, 1961 (Box 10)
  - Correspondence, Ca-Cole, 1961 (Box 10)
  - Correspondence, Colle-Colu, 1961 (Box 10)
  - Correspondence, Congress on the History of Art, 20th International, 1961 (Box 10)
  - Correspondence, Cons-Cun, 1961 (Box 10)
  - Correspondence, D-F, 1961 (Box 10)
  - Correspondence, G, 1961 (Box 10)
  - Correspondence, H-I, 1961 (Box 10)
  - Correspondence, J-L, 1961 (Box 10)
  - Correspondence, K-L, 1961 (Box 10)
  - Correspondence, McCormick, Thomas J., 1961 (Box 10)
  - Correspondence, M, 1961 (Box 10)
  - Correspondence, N-O, 1961 (Box 10)
  - Correspondence, P, 1961 (Box 10)
  - Correspondence, R, 1961 (Box 10)
  - Correspondence, Sa-Sk, 1961 (Box 10)
  - Correspondence, Sm-Sob, 1961 (Box 10)
  - Correspondence, Soc-Su, 1961 (Box 10)
  - Correspondence, T-V, 1961 (Box 10)
  - Correspondence, W, 1961 (Box 10)
  - Correspondence, X-Z, 1961 (Box 10)
  - Correspondence, Illegible and Unknown, 1961 (Box 10)
  - Correspondence, Al-Architectural, 1962 (Box 10)
  - Correspondence, "Architecture of H. H. Richardson and His Times" (reprint), 1962 (Box 10)
  - Correspondence, Architecture of the 19th and 20th Centuries (Pelican History of Art Series, 2nd Edition), 1962 (Box 10)
  - Correspondence, Ari-Au, 1962 (Box 10)
  - Correspondence, B, 1962 (Box 10)
  - Correspondence, C, 1962 (Box 10)
  - Correspondence, D-E, 1962 (Box 10)
  - Correspondence, F, 1962 (Box 10)
  - Correspondence, G, 1962 (Box 10)
  - Correspondence, H-I, 1962 (Box 10)
  - Correspondence, J, 1962 (Box 10)
  - Correspondence, K, 1962 (Box 10)
  - Correspondence, L, 1962 (Box 10)
  - Correspondence, Maa-Mac/Mc, 1962 (Box 11)
  - Correspondence, Man-Mi, 1962 (Box 11)
  - Correspondence, Mo, 1962 (Box 11)
  - Correspondence, Mu, 1962 (Box 11)
  - Correspondence, N-O, 1962 (Box 11)
  - Correspondence, P-Q, 1962 (Box 11)
  - Correspondence, R, 1962 (Box 11)
  - Correspondence, Sa-Sm, 1962 (Box 11)
  - Correspondence, Soc, 1962 (Box 11)
  - Correspondence, Som-Sw, 1962 (Box 11)
  - Correspondence, T-V, 1962 (Box 11)
  - Correspondence, W, 1962 (Box 11)
  - Correspondence, X-Z, 1962 (Box 11)
  - Correspondence, Illegible and Unknown, 1962 (Box 11)
  - Correspondence, A, 1963 (Box 11)
  - Correspondence, B, 1963 (Box 11)
  - Correspondence, C, 1963 (Box 11)
  - Correspondence, D-E, 1963 (Box 11)
  - Correspondence, F-G, 1963 (Box 11)
  - Correspondence, H, 1963 (Box 11)
  - Correspondence, J, 1963 (Box 11)
  - Correspondence, K-L, 1963 (Box 11)
  - Correspondence, M, 1963 (Box 11)
  - Correspondence, N-O, 1963 (Box 11)
  - Correspondence, P-Q, 1963 (Box 11)
  - Correspondence, R, 1963 (Box 11)
  - Correspondence, Sa-Sm, 1963 (Box 11)
  - Correspondence, So-St, 1963 (Box 11)
  - Correspondence, T, 1963 (Box 11)
  - Correspondence, W, 1963 (Box 11)
  - Correspondence, X-Z, 1963 (Box 11)
  - Correspondence, A, 1964 (Box 11)
  - Correspondence, A, 1964 (Box 11)
  - Correspondence, B, 1964 (Box 11)
  - Correspondence, Ca-Col, 1964 (Box 11)
  - Correspondence, Coo-Cu, 1964 (Box 11)
  - Correspondence, D-F, 1964 (Box 11)
  - Correspondence, G, 1964 (Box 11)
  - Correspondence, H-I, 1964 (Box 11)
  - Correspondence, J-L, 1964 (Box 11)
  - Correspondence, Ma, 1964 (Box 11)
  - Correspondence, Me-Mu, 1964 (Box 11)
  - Correspondence, N-O, 1964 (Box 12)
  - Correspondence, P, 1964 (Box 12)
  - Correspondence, R, 1964 (Box 12)
  - Correspondence, Sa-Sm, 1964 (Box 12)
  - Correspondence, So-Sw, 1964 (Box 12)
  - Correspondence, T-V, 1964 (Box 12)
  - Correspondence, W, 1964 (Box 12)
  - Correspondence, Zimmerman Brothers, 1964 (Box 12)
  - Correspondence, Zodiac Magazine, 1964 (Box 12)
  - Correspondence, Illegible and Unknown, 1964 (Box 12)
  - Correspondence, A, 1965 (Box 12)
  - Correspondence, B, 1965 (Box 12)
  - Correspondence, Banking, 1965 (Box 12)
  - Correspondence, Bills Paid, 1965, (2 folders) (Box 12)
  - Correspondence, Ca-Col, 1965 (Box 12)
  - Correspondence, Cooper Union, 1965 (Box 12)
  - Correspondence, Car (European), 1965 (Box 12)
  - Correspondence, D, 1965 (Box 12)
  - Correspondence, Deutsche Bank, 1965 (Box 12)
  - Correspondence, E-F, 1965 (Box 12)
  - Correspondence, G, 1965 (Box 12)
  - Correspondence, Cornell University - Cow, 1965 (Box 12)
  - Correspondence, H, 1965 (Box 12)
  - Correspondence, I-J, 1965 (Box 12)
  - Correspondence, K-L, 1965 (Box 12)
  - Correspondence, M, 1965 (Box 12)
  - Correspondence, N-O, 1965 (Box 12)
  - Correspondence, P-Q, 1965 (Box 12)
  - Correspondence, R, 1965 (Box 12)
  - Correspondence, Sa-Sm, 1965 (Box 12)
  - Correspondence, So, 1965 (Box 12)
  - Correspondence, St, 1965 (Box 12)
  - Correspondence, T-V, 1965 (Box 12)
  - Correspondence, W-Z, 1965 (Box 12)
  - Correspondence, Illegible and Unknown, 1965 (Box 12)
  - Correspondence, A, 1966 (Box 13)
  - Correspondence, B, 1966 (Box 13)
  - Correspondence, Banking, 1966 (Box 13)
  - Correspondence, Bills Paid, 1966 (Box 13)
  - Correspondence, C, 1966 (Box 13)
  - Correspondence, D, 1966 (Box 13)
  - Correspondence, E-F, 1966 (Box 13)
  - Correspondence, G, 1966 (Box 13)
  - Correspondence, H-I, 1966 (Box 13)
  - Correspondence, J-L, 1966 (Box 13)
  - Correspondence, Maa-Mac/Mc, 1966 (Box 13)
  - Correspondence, Mar-Mod, 1966 (Box 13)
  - Correspondence, Mor-Mu, 1966 (Box 13)
  - Correspondence, N-O, 1966 (Box 13)
  - Correspondence, Pa-Pe, 1966 (Box 13)
  - Correspondence, Pi-Pr, 1966 (Box 13)
  - Correspondence, Sa-Sob, 1966 (Box 13)
  - Correspondence, Soc, 1966 (Box 13)
  - Correspondence, Sou-St, 1966 (Box 13)
  - Correspondence, Q-R, 1966 (Box 13)
  - Correspondence, T, 1966 (Box 13)
  - Correspondence, Victorian Paperback, 1966 (Box 13)
  - Correspondence, Victorian Society, 1966 (Box 13)
  - Correspondence, W, 1966 (Box 13)
  - Correspondence, Y, 1966 (Box 13)
  - Correspondence, Zimmerman, 1966 (Box 13)
  - Correspondence, Zodiac Magazine, 1966 (Box 13)
  - Correspondence, Illegible and Unknown, 1966 (Box 13)
  - Correspondence, A-Architectural, 1967 (Box 13)
  - Correspondence, Architecture of the 19th and 20th Centuries (Pelican History of Art Series, 3rd Edition), 1967 (Box 13)
  - Correspondence, Architecture of the 19th and 20th Centuries (Pelican History of Art Series, Italian Edition), 1967 (Box 13)
  - Correspondence, Archon-Ay, 1967 (Box 13)
  - Correspondence, B, 1967 (Box 13)
  - Correspondence, Bills Paid, 1967 (Box 13)
  - Correspondence, C, 1967 (Box 13)
  - Correspondence, D, 1967 (Box 13)
  - Correspondence, F-G, 1967 (Box 13)
  - Correspondence, H, 1967 (Box 13)
  - Correspondence, I-K, 1967 (Box 13)
  - Correspondence, L, 1967 (Box 13)
  - Correspondence, McCormick, Thomas J., 1967 (Box 14)
  - Correspondence, M, 1967 (Box 14)
  - Correspondence, N-O, 1967 (Box 14)
  - Correspondence, P-Q, 1967 (Box 14)
  - Correspondence, R, 1967 (Box 14)
  - Correspondence, Sa-Sm, 1967 (Box 14)
  - Correspondence, Soc, 1967 (Box 14)
  - Correspondence, St-Sw, 1967 (Box 14)
  - Correspondence, T-Ve, 1967 (Box 14)
  - Correspondence, Vi-Vo, 1967 (Box 14)